Hey look these fish are really cute.
The Sakura sure is enjoying herself.
Yes she is.
She likes track meet and field trips and all that kind of stuff.
My name is Sakura Kinomoto.
I'm a fourth Grader at Tomoeda elementary school.
We're out on a social studies field trip today.
Each group went to a different public institution.
But we ended up going to the aquarium.
I love the aquarium.
The penguin shows about to start.
Okay okay.
Sakura that's...
Come on you guys.
Let's hurry.
Wow she's fast.
Penguins penguins penguins!
Sakura looks like she's having fun.
Sakura's Heart-Racing First Date
This is incredible.
Amazing.
I'd really love to swim with the penguins.
Well you are a very good swimmer Sakura.
There.
No, penguin keep away.
No penguin penguin.
Penguin.
I'm gonna save my penguin
No penguin.
What's going on?
A penguin's caught in the whirlpool.
But I can't get to him.
Wow.
That's my brother.
What?
Almost drowned? No you didn't.
That's not what I said.
You weren't even listening to me.
Oops.
Nobody was home.
So I thought I'd come out of your room for a change.
But I haven't been able to relax since.
Well that makes more sense.
You wouldn't be drowning.Would you Sakura?
Cause the one thing you're good at is sports.
What do you mean one thing?
You're not getting any cakes.
Oh please Sakura.
Anyway had penguin drowning.
That's really hard to believe.
The adults were wondering if maybe.
It was because the tank's plug had come out.
But that's not what it seem like to me.
Huh.
Here.
Actually no it wasn't like that at all.
It was more like...
It was more like something I should know.
What like when you see a clow card?
Huh.
I'm home.
Oh no.
Hurry get back to my room.
Hi.
Hi Touya.
Touya you're at the aquarium today weren't you.
Duh.
If you look it's written right there.
Touya I'm working at the aquarium.
Touya, how come you were at the penguin show?
What do you do?
Feed the penguins.
Really? That's so great.
No it isn't.
How come?
Just because.
No that's mine.
You can't just help yourself.
I saved up my allowance to buy that.
Hey what are you doing? Hurry up and come in.
Ahh?
I'm coming.
It took a while to get my shoes off.
Hello, how are you Sakura?
Yukito.
Hello.
Those look delicious.
You're a good cook aren't you Sakura.
No not really.
That's right she's really not.
Yeah.
Would would you like some hot cakes.
I just bake them.
You sure you bought them with your allowance right?
That's okay.
I'll bring them up to my brother's room later.
Okay.
Oh no.
I can't knock on the door.
What am I gonna do.
I'll be right there Sakura.
Oh Sakura I didn't know you were here.
Um.
How did you know I was here when I didn't even knock?
I had a feeling.
You said you brought this up for us right?
The aquarium.
Water.
Sakura.
Hey Sakura what on earth happened?
I'm so happy.
Oh Yukito.
Hey let me go.
Uh huh.
Stop acting so silly would ya.
What about your mission as the card captor Sakura?
I'm more interested in Yukito.
I see so you don't care if the penguin start drowning again.
Oh no that'd be awful.
I thought that was the end of me.
Well this might be a bit of a problem.
Uh.
Now then I suppose the thing that almost drowned the trainer
and the penguin was in the water.
That right?
Hmm.
Okay tell me what you saw.
Did you see this thing while they were drowning?
I didn't.The water was just swirling around.
Then it's probably the water card.
I thought so.
So we just catch it and turn it back into a card.
It's not that easy.
We can't see the water card when it's in the water.
And even if we're able to pull it out of the water.
If it separates in different directions.
We won't be able to control it.
It's hard to catch things like water that don't have a shape.
The water card has stronger magic
than some of the other clow cards.
It's difficult to use the four basic elements.
Earth, water, fire and wind.
And water is a card of untamed magic.
It has a very wild nature.
The cards you have so far are windy, fly and shadow.
But this one is beyond your power.
Even if you use windy.
Which has the same high strength of magic as water.
Windy wouldn't beat it because windy's kind.
Windy shadow fly.
Do we only have these three cards?
How can I catch water.
Come on.
I've got to do something quick and catch the water card.
You seem down.
What's wrong Sakura?
No, I'm fine really.
Uh.
Seems like you've got a big challenge ahead
for the pact you made with the allies of justice.
Hmm.
Yes I guess a clow card is behind all of this.
Yeah but Kero says that it's not gonna be as easy as all that.
Hmm.
Tomoyo.
Yes.
Thanks for hearing me out.
You look so good when you smile like that.
Oh yeah this is for you.
This is a new product for my mom's company.
Here this one is for you.
And here's another one for Kero.
You sure we can have them?
Of course.
By the way my mother wants you to tell her how you like it.
Thanks for thinking of me.
Well see you tomorrow.
Yeah see ya.
But if we put all three cards together then sure.
It won't work.
No matter what you do with those cards you have.
Hmm hmm.
But the water card.
It's out there.
This is terrible.
Ah.
Are you okay Sakura?
Yu Yukito.
You should watch where you're going.
Yes I'm sorry.
Thanks for the cake yesterday they were delicious.
No not at all.
You're late. Have you just left your club?
You're in the cheerleaders club right?
Uh yeah.
Touya told me you hit him with your baton while practicing at home.
Touya how could you tell Yukito such a thing.
Can I take you out for a meal to eat to thank you for the cakes.
Really? Are you sure?
I found a place that's pretty good.
Let's meet tomorrow at one at the penguin park okay.
Sure!
Ah.
Oh Yukito.
Oh not that again Sakura.
Hello Daidouji residents.
No one's able to take your call right now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Hi Tomoyo guess what?
I'm going on a date tomorrow with Yukito.
We're meeting at one. I'm so excited.
I'll call you when I get back.
Um.
I was just wondering did I get the time wrong.
You're fifteen minutes early.
What about you?
I didn't want to keep you waiting Sakura.
So I got here early.
Hey this is...
Oh that's right.
You were just here the other day.
Weren't you?
Are we going in here.
That's right.
Aha.
So that's the aquarium.
This is just perfect.
You can check it the clow cards in here.
Yes and I can capture Sakura's first date on tape.
Hmm.
Heh heh heh.
Yeah do it.
What a huge fish huh.
Sure is.
I wonder if it's edible.
One person couldn't eat the whole thing.
I'm not so sure about that.
Oh?
Boy this is so touching.
Geez don't kids hold hands these days.
And candy bear.
Hey kid lay another finger on me and you'll get hurt.
They have moved on to another place.
See you around.
Wow this is a real.
I didn't see any of this last time.
Cause of what happened to the penguins.
So I guess you didn't know there was a tea room.
Ah.
You can sit there and watch all the fish. Touya.
Uh, Touya.
Are you working with the penguins anymore?
They drained out all the water and are gonna do an inspection.
Huh.
Then what about the water card.
Must be nice not working in the freezer anymore.
That penguin food was locked up in the freezer.
Touya said it was really cold.
It doesn't really make any difference.
Cause now I'm in charge of making shaved ice.
A strawberry shaved ice here is really good.
Ah.
Shaved ice.
Ice.
Bring us two please.
Okay.
You want an extra large.
Uh is there such a thing.
What?
Is this a chaperone date or what?
Sakura!
The water card.
Sakura. Yukito.
Sakura.
Are you all right Sakura?
Tomoyo.
Oh yeah.
Where's Yukito?
Glad you're okay.
I thought I was gonna die.
Is this what I think.
Yeah the clow card is behind this.
The water card is definitely here.
You saw it.
Hey wait a minute what are you two doing here.
Are you all right, Sakura?
Yeah.
Too bad we didn't get to have that shaved ice after all.
That's okay.
Shaved ice.
Shaved ice ice.
Aha.
Yukito thank you so much.
Right.
There are 25.
Good night.
Right good night sir.
You're gonna enjoy this pro baseball broadcast and now.
Here's your daily.
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
No problem.
Here?
This is where the magic feels the strongest.
It's there.
Daidouji here.
Got it.
Yeah on the first floor of the basement.
Great now go ahead.
Water.
Come out.
Get back Kero.
Fly!
Nice job Sakura.
Now It'll be easy to catch the water card once it's frozen.
It was Yukito who told me about the freezer where the animal food is.
Thanks for your help Tomoyo.
I'm just glad I was able to help.
Well now it's about time don't you think.
Now return to your true form clow card.
You are clever to have thought of that.
It's all thanks to Yukito.
Yukito.
Oh man I think Sakura's frozen too.
Hey take one for me too well don keep it up Sakura.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Have you all been doing your homework?
Yeah.
Well that's good to hear.
Time for my very popular time slot.
Kero's corner.
Alright then kids let's see what I have for you today.
This week we saw another of Sakura's battle costumes
just like we did last week.
This videotape you're looking at now.
Was all recorded by Sakura's friend Tomoyo.
Boy, she's pretty good with the camera isn't she.
No wonder she's Sakura's number one camera crew.
But how was she able to capture all this on tape.
Hmm.
And now a costume checked by Kero.
First the jester's hat with a pompom on each end.
And the jester's shoes with pompoms too.
For the cloth you'll need something that's waterproof.
Okay well.
I think I'd better sign off now.
If I tell you too much today.
Then you'll have nothing to look forward to next time.
Hey, am I nice or what?
See ya.
Kero and I were cleaning together.
Then all of a sudden.
A big tree started growing out of the basement.
And our house was like a jungle.
How come?
Wait, is this because of the clow cards I found in the basement?
Next on card captor Sakura
Sakura's exhausting Sunday
Release!