Hello, is someone there?
I'm ready.
Sakura and the Strange Magical Book
Morning already.
Sakura, your breakfast is ready.
Right!
My name is Sakura Kinomoto.
I'm a fourth grader at Tomoeda elementary school.
I like PE and music I hate math.
I'm a very energetic girl. And for my family
Good morning!
What's with all the stomping around?
I wasn't stomping!
Sounds like you were stomping from down here.
Well I wasn't stomping alright?
So you keep saying.
But you sound like a monster when you walk around.
I am not a monster!
This mean person is my older brother Touya.
He's in grade 11
and goes to a high school next to my elementary school.
He's always teasing me just because he's a little taller than I am.
It really bugs me.
One day I'll grow ten times taller than him and squash him like a little bug!
Sweet revenge.
Nice to see you two getting along.
That's my dad Fujitaka.
He's a professor of archaeology at the university.
And not only is he very caring but he's a great cook.
I love him.
Here you are.
It looks great.
Thank you dad!
And that's my family.
What? My mom?
My mom passed away when I was three years old.
But don't feel bad for me.
I've got the greatest dad in the world and my brother's okay too, sometimes.
How is it? Great!
I'm done.
What? You're leaving?
Soccer practice.
Here. Thanks dad.
See ya.
Hey, wait a second.
Thanks for breakfast.
You've finished already?
Well, here's your lunch.
Where's Touya?
He left already.
Do you have cheer leading today?
Yeah see ya.
Bye
Where did he go?
Right, got him.
Wait for me.
You know Sakura you can leave for school much later.
I know.
But then I wouldn't be able to see him.
Hey Yukito!
Oh, good morning.
Hey.
Morning Touya.
Good morning Sakura you're up early.
Yeah.
You should have seen her gulping down her breakfast.
I guess she showed him who's boss.
This is Yukito.
He's in the same grade as my brother.
I can't believe that two of them are friends.
He's so nice and caring.
Not at all like my brother and he's so cute.
Well, see you Sakura.
We're here already.
See you later.
He's so sweet.
He's quite a hunk.
Tomoyo?
Giving you a present as he's leaving he's quite a charmer.
Yeah.
Good morning Tomoyo, how are you today?
I'm well and a good morning to you.
This is Tomoyo, she's my best friend.
She's smart and beautiful.
And her father owns a really big company.
You should have seen your face it was so cute.
That candy in your hand and the look of love all over your face.
Was it really that obvious?
I just wish I had a camera to capture such a beautiful moment.
Good idea.
Tomoyo loves to take pictures and make videos.
And I'm one of her favorite models.
Hey Sakura
my dad just bought me a new video camera.
Do you think I could film you next time?
But there must be something more interesting for you
to make a video of than me.
But then look on your face
while you were holding that candy was so sweet and loving.
I'll bring the video camera with me tomorrow.
She's sweet
but a little weird.
And there he appeared a wild look in his eyes
his mouth gaping from the surprise.
But who wouldn't have been.
Had there ever been such a large orange.
That was such a strange dream.
That's a very cute drawing Sakura. What is it this?
This? Well it's...
Sakura? Yes.
Please read it aloud.
I'll tell you later.
Start from the 12th line.
There's no doubt the orange was something special.
But what came out was stranger.
WOW!
That's great  Sakura! Amazing!
Thank you for that Sakura.
Next we will practice our baton twirling.
Please collect your batons and line up.
Yeah.
That dream is still bothering me.
I'll ask Tomoyo what she thinks about it.
I've never seen Sakura drop her baton before. She's a pro.
But sometimes she's a real clutz.
I'm home.
I'll be home at 9.
Oh, dad's gonna be late tonight.
Is someone there?
I wish dad and Touya would come home now.
It's coming from dad's library.
Oh no what if it's a robber?
I'll peek through the door.
And if someone's there. I'll call the police.
There's no one down here.
The book from my dream.
It's a card.
Wind?
That's weird.
Wind
Windy
What just happened?
Hidey-howdy-ho!!
Wow, Thanks a lot for finally waking me up.
Waking you?
Yeah, I've been stuck inside that book for a really long time.
It feels good to get out and stretch a bit.
What are you?
A squirrel? Stop that! Is that a new toy?
I'm not a toy.
I am the guardian beast of the seal of this book.
I am Cerberus.
The seal? Cerberus?
Correct.
It is my job to protect all the cards in this book from getting into trouble.
Where did they go?
Not here! Not there! where did all the cards go?
Here.
Oh yes, this is a card. Oh thank goodness.
Well, where are the others?
Well, when I read the word windy,
this spin wind started blowing.
They all blew away.
Oh right. hahahahaha.
Say whaaaaaaat?
Well I'm done.
Where are you taking that?
I'll eat it while I'm studying.
Well, no good.
I can't get a sense of where any of them are.
Here. That looks delicious.
But I'm not hungry. You see this book contain the clow cards.
What are they?
They're dangerous.
The clow cards were all created by an old wizard named Clow Reed.
Every one of the cards has its own character
and is very powerful.
They have the ability to take over the world doing whatever they want.
Almost nothing can stop them.
But luckily before they could do any damage.
Clow Reed managed to capture them.
He made the book to keep the cards in.
Then made a special seal and me as the guardian of that seal.
I've got to get those cards back.
And you are going to help.
Why do I have to?
Well, You're the one that unleash them when you use the wind spell.
But you told me it was your job to guard the seal
and make sure the clow cards didn't escape from the book.
Well, I guess I was sleeping.
How long?
Thirty years.
And they made you the book's guardian?
I was tired! very tired!
So the noise I heard was you snoring.
Yes, but what's important is that you could open the book
which means that you possess magical powers.
So tell me your name.
I'm Sakura.
Well, Sakura. Stand over there.
Key of the seal.
This girl will carry out the secret promise.
Her name is Sakura.
Key, bestow her with magical powers. Release the power!
Sakura, take the wand.
That's it.
You have now become the card captor.
Whaaaaaat?
I can't do this.
I really can't do it.
What a soft bed!
Hey, I can't be a card captor.
Is that clear?
Card captor, the one who catches the magical card doesn't that sounds cool.
I'm an elementary school student.
And I won't be responsible for the fate of the world.
Don't forget it was your fault for losing the cards in the first place.
Well I wouldn't tell if the guardian hadn't been asleep.
What a strong wind!
Sakura!
What is that?
it's a clow card. What?
That one is the fly card.
Don't just stand there, move!
Do what?
This will be the first mission of the card captor.
What?
You could have at least let me get changed.
The card capture must be prepared for battle at all times.
It's so big, I can't catch that.
You're the card capture!
Now use your magic.
Like I showed you, take out the key and say the spell.
Reveal your secret powers.
Reveal your true powers to me.
My name is Sakura and I command you
RELEASE!
Okay Sakura the fly card belongs to the wind category.
You should be able to catch it using the windy card.
Are you sure?
We're going to have to get much closer though.
Oh no, it's coming back.
Quickly use the windy card.
Hurry up it's coming back again.
Come on Sakura use the windy card.
Here it comes.
I can't do it.
You're the card captor if you can't stop it no one can.
Yeah but how?
I got an idea.
Where are you going?
Sakura!
Wind, form a chain to bind this bird.
I am Sakura the card captor and I command you to return to me now.
Hey good job Sakura.
I thought I was gonna die.
Oh you'll be okay. You're the card captor.
Forget it! I Don't want anything to do with this insanity.
If you think that was insane waiting till you meet a few of the stronger cards.
Well you've just captured the fly card.Why Don't you try it out?
Well I guess it wouldn't hurt.
Now that's the spirit.
Fly!
Now isn't that better?
Yeah.
You know we make a great team, card captor Sakura.
I told you I never agreed to be the card captor!
Hidey-howdy-ho!!
My name is Cerberus and I'm the host of Kero's corner.
A little extra dedicated to all the fans of card captor Sakura.
And each episode I'll be coming to you with something different from the show.
Today for your pleasure. Ta-da!
The Tomoeda school uniform.
There's two types
one with long sleeves and one with short sleeves.
As you can see, this is the long sleeve model.
It's navy blue and a super elegant design.
If you look on our left arm. You'll see the school logo.
And don't forget the really cute hat.
And now a costume check by Kero.
Today's costume check is the skirt.
Don't you think the white pleated skirt looks nice on Sakura?
This is the boys uniform.
That brings to a close of today's Kero's corner.
I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did.
And don't worry, I'll keep you updated with all the latest changes. See-ya!
I barely captured the fly card.
So I really don't think I can handle the job of card captor.
If my friends find out.
I'll have some big problems.
On top of that, Tomoyo says that she has a video that she wants to show me.
Don't miss the next episode of Card Captor Sakura.
Sakura's fabulous friends.
Release!