Sakura's Fabulous Friends
Sakura
I couldn't eat another bite.
Hey you're the one that wanted to get up early.
Now come on! It's seven AM.
That's a funny voice. It's not my dad or my brother.
Maybe it's the TV.
Oh, it's not on.
Well, what's that voice?
Ha ha!
What's wrong?
A stuffed animal?
You're still half asleep.
Wake up sleepy head.
ah ah oh yeah
You're the keeper the clow cards.
Glad it's all coming back.
I am Cerberus, the guardian beast.
I remember though I can't say I understand any of this.
It all happened
when I found a glowing book in the basement yesterday.
I accidentally let the magic cards out.
And now it's my task to gather them all back up.
What a beautiful morning card captor Sakura.
I told you I can't be the card captor.
hahaha
Well sure you can.
see
You've already recaptured the fly card.
See you look.
But I almost got killed!
Breakfast is ready!
Coming!
Good morning Touya.
You're actually ready on time
or maybe I'm late.
I had someone to wake me up all right
huh
I mean the alarm clock silly.
Hi mom good morning.
Well good morning.
Hi, morning dad.
Morning.
Well this looks great.
It's because the monster didn't touch it.
Well it's getting cold shall we eat now.
I finished.
You're up early today Sakura.
I'm on cleaning duty at the school.
huh
Weird kid.
You're back.
I brought you something.
ah
wow
I'm going now.
You sure do go to school early.
Touya and dad will go to school pretty soon.
Once they're gone
you can turn on the TV or something.
So your dad's still a student?
He's a university professor.
It would be better if you stayed up here while they're home.
I think you'd scare them.
Sure!
huh
Is that the time? See you later!
See ya!
I'll take a shortcut.
hahaha
This is Yukito's house.
I guess he's not around.
Hello
You scared me.
Morning Sakura.
Oh morning Yukito.
You're early.
I'm on cleaning duty.
Alright
Ah I forgot!
For your classroom.
Are you sure?
hmm
wow
Oh thank you so much for these.
Nice to see you again.
Thanks again!
See ya!
He's wonderful.
Yes! I made it first.
Hey you're here early. Morning.
Good morning Tomoyo.
It's beautiful outside.
Are you on cleaning duty as well this morning.
That's next week.
I came in early because I have something I wanted to show you.
huh
A video? Just watch.
I took it last night.
And what was that?
Let me show you my favorite part.
Did you find another clow card?
Which one is it? Get ready we have no time to lose.
oh
hey
Wow it's you.
It's hot in there.
Why did you hide in there?
Well, I wanted to see what a typical day in the card captor's life was like.
ah
Come on Sakura, aren't you gonna introduce us.
He says his name is Cerberus.
He doesn't look like a Cerberus to me.
More like a Kero Chan, right?
Much better.
My name is not up for discussion.
I am Cerberus
the guardian of the seal
the protector of the clow cards.
Clow cards?
Hey, try this.
And that Tomoyo is how Sakura became the card captor.
That's just incredible.
The card captor is here to protect our town
from the disastrous clow cards.
That's so cool.
Come on Tomoyo. I can't do anything like that.
Oh no I'm sure you can.
Do you think you could show me some of your special magic Sakura.
What?
That's a great idea Tomoyo.
But.
This is perfect. No one's around but us three.
um
Reveal your secret powers.
Reveal your true power to me.
My name is Sakura and I command you.
RELEASE!
Is that your magic staff for spells.
Well I need the cards too.
You mean this.
Is that safe?
So do you have a special pose too?
A special what?
Cause all magical girls have special poses for their spells.
bye bye
bye bye see you later
goodbye
I'll give you a call again.
see you tomorrow
okay bye
see you later
yeah
Morning. Hey. What are you doing?
oh morning morning
What's going on?
Oh, hi Sakura.
Look!
What happened here?
I don't know.
It was like this when we got here.
ah ah
Who would do such an awful thing?
More importantly
this is going to take us a really long time to clean up again.
ah
ah?
Morning Tomoyo.
Good morning.
Wow this shirt is a big mess.
I wonder who could have done all this
Do you think maybe this is the doing of one of the clow cards.
huh
hmm
Yep, that's a clow card alright.
Knew it.
It made a huge mess.
Took us forever to clean it up.
At least we got out of math class this morning.
Oh yeah I guess that was kind of nice.
So what kind of clow card
would cause that sort of miss to the school?
hmm
I don't know.
Alright Sakura.
It's time to be the card captor.
But why me?
If it's the work of a clow card.
You're the only one who can catch it.
I don't wanna be the card captor.
Well then you shouldn't have let them all out.
Get ready because we're taking back the school tonight.
What? Tonight?
Not a chance!
Why not?
Well, because it's really scary.
oh
There's no way I'm going there at night.
A lot of the cards don't come out until night.
You better get used to it.
It could be quite dangerous in the school at night.
Oh, Tomoyo.
So in that case I better come with you.
I'll be there to capture your brave and selfless deeds on my video.
But how come?
Because making videos is my passion.
Alright, tonight the three of us take the school.
In that case
we'd better get to work on your cute magical girl pose.
Right.
Training starts now.
No.
I'm scared.
Don't worry I'm right here what could go wrong.
Hahahaha!
You're not making me feel better.
huh huh
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, we just got here too.
huh
They take me everywhere.
These are my private bodyguards.
Goodbye miss. Careful.
Thanks, I'll call you when I need to be picked up.
wow
That's so cool!
There aren't very many school kids
who have their own bodyguards.
Oh yeah.
Well, there are even fewer who have their own magical powers.
Yes so.
Now then come with me.
Wow, what's this?
Time for you to get changed.
What? But why?
Well you're going into the school to catch the next clow card.
Aren't you?
I guess.
You can't be a magical super girl without the right outfit.
What?
Now, that's the spirit.
You want the clow cards to know
they're dealing with someone special.
You can't be outshine by those silly cards.
Oh I couldn't have said it better myself.
So, time to get changed.
I've got a really great hat.
Come on, in you go.
You look fabulous so cute.
This is embarrassing.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Hmm, that's right.
I have something for you to wear.
Huh, for me?
Wow.
You two look so much cuter now that you match.
You think so.
I won't be cute if I die.
What do you guys think that noise was?
You heard something?
I think I can feel a clow card.
Let's go home.
Calm down.
Did you just see that?
That big statue is floating.
Look Sakura, look.
A shadow but no body.
A shadow?
Are you sure this is one of the clow cards?
Positive.
The shadow card is doing this.
Cerberus take Tomoyo somewhere safe.
It's time Sakura.
Reveal your secret powers.
Reveal your true power to me.
My name is Sakura and I command you
RELEASE!
looking good.
Wind card form a chain to bind the shadow, Windy!
Quickly Sakura use your fly card and get out of there.
Fly!
wow
The shadow card must have gathered together
the shadows of all the students at the school.
It's using them all against the Sakura.
It's just too many for her to fight.
Is there some other way for her to fight them?
Well if the shadows of the students are struck by light.
They will all disappear leaving only the bad shadow for Sakura to fight.
But the problem is that it's night right now.
Leave that part to me.
I've got a good idea.
I told you I couldn't deal with this.
What am I gonna do?
Hey, let go of me!
ah ah
ah
Somebody help me!
huh
The shadows are gone.
Sakura.
They all just disappeared,
All about the bad shadow disappear when they're struck by light.
And we couldn't wait for the sun to come out.
So we decided to turn on every light in the school instead.
Oh thank you Tomoyo.
huh
Sakura, I can see the bad shadow.
This is your chance to catch it.
Let's see if all that training paid off.
Wind card form a chain to bind.
windy
Time to return to your true form.
Clow card!
Alright!
Victory two for Sakura the card captor.
Looking good Sakura.
Hey, Chiharu have you seen Tomoyo?
I think she's in the audio visual room.
Thanks a lot.
Tomoyo, thank you so much for helping me.
I got you a little... ah
What?
What a true masterpiece of film.
So you actually got all that on your camera?
Of course.
I didn't miss a single second of your heroism last night.
And I hope from now on you'll take me along with you
when you catch clow cards.
What?
I wanna have all the card captor's bravery captured forever.
ahaha Tomoyo
also
I'd like to be in charge of your outfits from now on.
I've got some fabulous ideas on how to use a lot more ribbons.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
How are you all?
And welcome to the second edition of Kero's corner.
That little extra that delves into the finer points of our show.
So without further ado.
Let's see what we have for you today.
This time we saw the appearance of Sakura's battle costume.
A real masterpiece made by her friend Tomoyo.
This is Tomoyo Daidouji.
She's more than just a pretty face.
She's a smart fourth grader.
Not only is she good at everything
but her newest hobby is making the costumes that Sakura will wear into battle
then filming the entire event on her video camera.
And now today's costume check.
Today it's the hat Sakura wear in the battle
with long ribbons ending in gold ornaments.
Honorable mention goes to her great kit.
Well that's all the time we have today.
But I hope to see you next time
when we'll be taking another extra special look
into the amazing costumes on card captor Sakura.
See ya!
It's like a dream come true.
I'm going to the aquarium with Yukito.
But trouble arrives when a clow card suddenly shows up.
There's no way I'm letting that thing spoil my date with Yukito.
Next time on card captor Sakura.
Sakura's exciting date
Release!