Great it's sunny today.
You're right. The rain last night seems like a dream.
Anyway Sakura.
You're up early today considering it's a Sunday.
Hahaha.
Uh.
I'm going on a picnic with Tomoyo to a park in the woods.
Hey. Why don't you come with us Kero.
If you stay in my backpack nobody will notice okay.
I'm so glad the weather cleared up.
Sakura's Exhausting Sunday
Good morning!
Good morning Sakura.
Pretty happy today huh monster.
I'll let you get away with that today.
Huh.
Yes you do seem to be in a good mood Sakura.
Haha sure I do. I'm going out with Tomoyo today.
But.
Ah.
You're doing all the housework today remember?
You traded with me last week don't you remember?
Weekend has a piano concert.
I sure like to goes here.
So which you mind...
Okay i'll trade with you.
Huh you will.
But on one condition in exchange.
You'll have to do all the housework next Sunday.
Okay.
Well I'm off to work.
Okay see ya.
Sorry.
The laundry's really piled up since it's been raining so much.
Listen, do you want me to help you?
You've got an academic meeting today.
Don't worry I'll be okay dad.
Sorry about this.
No problem.
All right then I'll leave this by the washing machine.
Okay.
See ya.
Bye Touya.
I'll be going as well.
Hmm.
Have a good day.
See you later.
Oh is that right.
I'm really sorry.
I completely forgot it was my turn to do the housework today.
It's okay it's not your fault.
I'm really sorry though.
Don't worry about it. Good luck with all your housework.
Thanks Tomoyo.
Well see you at school tomorrow.
Yeah see you soon.
Poor Tomoyo, I'll give her a call tomorrow to apologize.
Well then time to get started.
Kero, you okay?
Just because there's nobody around at home.
How come I'm stuck doing this kind of stuff.
Ah.
The wood.
This is a clow card.
Huh it stopped.
Kero Kero.
Yeah whoa.
Kero I found a clow card.
Uh huh.
He's not here. Well okay.
I'll brag about it later.
Uh.
What a daisy day it is!
Right that's enough.
This isn't the kind of stuff that I should be doing.
Oh yeah.
After we finished I'll have a popsicle with Kero.
Oh well I guess I can help out a little longer.
Right this is the last place to do.
Oh no it's covered in ink.
Ah.
This is a clow card too.
This is my lucky day.
I found two cards one after the other.
Oh.
I'll clean them.
With towel with towel.
Oh the phone.
Okay I'm coming.
Hello, who...
Sakura?
Uh yes dad?
Could you see if there's a blue envelope on top of the table.
Yeah there is.
Sorry but could you bring it to the bus stop for me.
The materials for my lecture are in there.
I'll be right there.
Kero I'm just going out for a bit.
What's going on?
Bye dad.
Thanks a lot.
Sakura.
Ah.
Ah hi Yukito.
That was your dad wasn't it.
Everything okay yeah.
My dad forgot something that's all.
So you brought it to him.
Good girl.
Huh.
You're in your uniform.
Oh.
Yeah there was a basketball game today.
So I was just helping out.
Actually Yukito doesn't belong in any clubs.
But he helps out sometimes as an assistant when there's a game or something.
Oh he's so smart and he could do anything.
Hey Sakura have you had lunch?
No not yet.
Wanna eat together? Right over there.
That's Touya.
Oh thanks.
That's your third plate.
He's three times as much as I do.
Three times?
Go on eat as much as you like Sakura.
It's my treat okay.
Kero's waiting for me at home so.
Oh who's Kero.
Oh nobody hahaha.
Well it's good to have a big appetite.
It's healthy.
It's hard on the allowance though.
Yukito.
Thanks for forgetting your things dad.
I got to run into Yukito.
I'm home.
Kero.
Thank you Kero.
You sleep some more.
I'll make your lunch right away.
Kero.
Kero wake up.
What? Is it time for lunch.
What's that sound?
Sound?
Is it a burglar.
It's coming from downstairs.
I hope it's not a ghost.
Think a ghost would be here in the daytime?
Who knows, it might.
It's in the basement.
It's in there.
Go on.
Oh it's hard to see anything.
What the heck is that.
That's just a branch from a plant.
What's something like that doing coming up from the basement.
Hey the wood card is behind this.
The clow card?
Oh that reminds me now.
What?
You just left the clow cards you found without writing your name on them?
But they were still in the shape of cards when I found them.
And and then the phone just rang.
That's no good.
The cards will only listen to the person
who's the first to write down their names on the cards.
But they've been in the house all this time.
And nothing happens up until now.
Hmm.
And the wood card is such a gentle one too.
I can't imagine it doing anything bad.
Then what's happened.
Hmm.
Oh no Kero don't let go.
Kero do something quickly.
I can't do a thing. The things got me too.
What do I do?
I wonder who it is?
Who? You'll know when they come in.
If someone sees us like this the whole town will be talking.
And Kero they might think you're talking teddy bear.
Will try to sell you or something.
That'd be the worst.
Uh coming.
Why'd you answer them.
Come to think of it, it wouldn't be so bad.
Kero.
You shouldn't be talking to teddy bears.
You're mean.
Oh this isn't what it seems.
Hello?
Ah ah Tomoyo.
I thought it come over and help you with your housework.
Have you been pruning the garden?
No the clow card wood is behind this.
Oh.
Sakura now is the time to use the seal.
RELEASE.
Return to your true form now.
Clow card.
That's fantastic Sakura.
What's wrong is something the matter.
The card's not here.
That can't be.
It must have fallen around here somewhere.
How about over in that room.
Oh yeah the basement.
Good let's go get that card.
Yeah.
Sakura.
It seems to have stop now.
Yeah it seems to be happy having the sunlight on it.
Yes just like a wood card.
The laundry it's ruined.
Oh no.
No I have to start all over again.
Don't let it get you down Kero.
I'll help you out okay.
Oh I have to start all over.
Anyway what are we gonna do about this.
If I use the seal it'll just go back to its former state.
Of course it will.
Go and get the card now and let's finish sealing it up.
You mean go to the basement?
Right.
What's that sound?
Sounds just like an outfit walking.
No it's the house creaking.
The tree is still growing.
But it was quiet up to a minute ago.
Do you think it's figured out the light comes from outside.
Yeah now it wants to get the light to its whole body.
It'll destroy the house.
No.
It's time for us occur on the card captor.
Hmm why did you bring this clothes over?
I want to make a video of you dancing.
And doing your magic and your battle dress in this wonderful jungle.
And look she's made this lunch for us too.
You can get through here.
Ah.
This way.
Just a little further.
Ah ah.
We better hurry.
What's that sound?
I'm not sure.
Oh water.
The water can't possibly come from the wood card.
So It's from the other card.
What's that? You mean there were two cards?
Yeah.
So that means...
Oh.
Hey it was rain.
Rain?
Yes.
The rain card.
The rain card got together with the wood card.
And they created this jungle.
You ready?
Yeah.
The cold at moment.
Rain wood.
That's as far as you're gonna get.
Looking good.
Sakura it's coming.
Alright this isn't bad at all.
Uh huh.
Sakura hurry. It's just toying with you use the seal.
Sure but.
Okay.
Hey I know, go after the wood card.
Try going after with water.
Water card.
Right.
Oh darkness that created the cards.
Lend me the power of the key.
And give me the power.
To transfer the magical powers of the card to this key.
Water!
A water become a chain of restrain.
Alright you got it.
Return to your true form now.
Clow card.
Hey you did it.
Okay next.
I have to take care of the one that tried to destroy our house.
Wait, hang on a second.
See I told you it was a gentle card didn't I.
I guess rain and wood really are good friends.
Oh.
Hey look at that!
Ah a rainbow.
It's beautiful.
Sakura done.
If you had written your name on the cards earlier.
We wouldn't have had all that trouble you know.
Yeah.
I've learned my lesson now.
In that case I'll get myself some shut-eye.
Good night.
Sorry about all this.
Not at all.
I got much better film on video
than what I would have gotten in the park you know.
Oh I see.
Sakura, come quickly.
Oh no.
I'll have to clean all over again.
Don't worry I'll help you Sakura.
Oh thank you so much.
I'm home. I'm home.
Thanks for doing all the housework.
We'll have some cake later on.
Better write your name on it or shall wolf it all down.
I did write my name. I did.
Hidey-howdy-ho!
Have you all been brushing your teeth properly?
It's time for the very popular time.
Slot of Cerberus the dandy Kero's corner.
Let's see what I have for you today.
This week we saw another of Sakura's battle costumes.
Make sure you listen to my description okay.
This costume was made with a theme of wings as you can see here.
The colors are pretty cute don't you think.
And the whole costume is made of rubber as well.
The shoes are safe and comfy high cut shoes.
And the gloves have this guard on them for protection.
Go go costume check.
The thing to note this time is the cute feathers on her head.
It's just like a headband.
Oops looks like our time is up.
Well are you getting familiar with my show.
There's lots of good things coming up in the future.
So I hope you'll look forward to it.
See ya.
A stuffed toy shop called the twin bells has just opened up.
Hey maybe I'll go there with Chiharu.
But Tomoyo tells me there's a strange rumor about the shop.
And that rumor will be left to card captor Sakura.
Next episode
Sakura and the panda and the wonderful store.
Release!